Guide to the Deep Dish TV Records MSS.312
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III. Events, 1981-2015; 9 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes and 5 flat boxes; 17 U-matic; 207 MiniDV; 2 DVCAM; 628.4 Gigabytes in 1,704 files
  - New Democratic Party Convention -- New Democracy, Environment and Energy, May 15, 2004 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1455, 312_1456)
  - New Democratic Party Convention -- New Democracy, Healthcare, May 15, 2004 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1457, 312_1458)
  - New Democratic Party Convention -- New Democracy, Urban Policy, May 15, 2004 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1459, 312_1460)
  - Jimmy Massey Testimonies, Florence, MA, August 5, 2004; cuid39626 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_392)
  - Take Back Democracy Film Festival, September 10-11, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 34)
  - Readings from Voices of a People's History of the United States, New York City, October 22, 2004; cuid39586 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_285)
  - Workshop on Archaeology and Computers, November 3 - 7, 2004 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1760, 312_1761, 312_1762, 312_1763, 312_1764, 312_1765, 312_1766, 312_1767, 312_1768, 312_1769, 312_1771, 312_1775, 312_1776, 312_1780, Box 161, Minidv 312_1790)
  - National Council on Family Relations Media Awards Competition, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 35)
  - The New York Video Festival, 2004 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - International Commission of Inquiry on Crimes Against Humanity of Bush Administration, 2004-2006; cuid39587 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_286)
  - Party, September 13, 2005 (Box 152, Minidv 312_1260)
  - Youth Conference, October 18, 2005 (Box 151, Minidv 312_1195)
  - ETV Input Conference Finalist Films, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 36)
  - Left Forum, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 37)
  - Dahr Jamail Lecture, Sacramento, California, March 14, 2006; cuid39627 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_393)
  - Environmental Justice for All Bus Tours, September 24 - October 1, 2006; cuid39581 (Box 53, Folder 1, Box 142, Minidv 312_1887, Box 162, Minidv 312_1968, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_287)
  - Environmental Justice for All Northeast Tour -- Buffalo, New York, September 24, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1936, 312_1937, 312_1939)
  - Environmental Justice for All Northeast Tour -- Syracuse and Endicott, New York, September 25, 2006 (Box 161, Minidv 312_1895, 312_1906, 312_1912)
    Syracuse 9-12, Endicott, NY 2:30-5
  - Environmental Justice for All Northeast Tour -- Albany, New Haven, and Hartford, September 26-27, 2006 (Box 161, Minidv 312_1896, 312_1897, 312_1898, 312_1899, 312_1901, 312_1910)
  - Environmental Justice for All Northeast Tour -- Newark, Northern New Jersey, Camden, September 26-29, 2006 (Box 161, Minidv 312_1900, 312_1903, 312_1904, 312_1908, 312_1909, Box 162, Minidv 312_1920)
  - Environmental Justice for All Northeast Tour -- New York City, September 28, 2006 (Box 161, Minidv 312_1907, Box 162, Minidv 312_1926)
  - Environmental Justice for All Northeast Tour -- Linden, New Jersey, September 30, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1915, 312_1917, 312_1918, 312_1919)
  - Environmental Justice for All Northeast Tour -- Boston, circa September, 2006 (Box 161, Minidv 312_1911)
  - Environmental Justice for All Northeast Tour -- Washington DC, circa September-October, 2006 (Box 161, Minidv 312_1891, 312_1925)
  - Environmental Justice for All Northeast Tour -- Wilmington, circa September-October, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1947, 312_1948)
  - Environmental Justice for All Northeast Tour, September 27 - October 1, 2006 (Box 161, Minidv 312_1902, 312_1913, 312_1914, Box 162, Minidv 312_1927, 312_1928, 312_1929)
  - Environmental Justice for All West Coast Tour, September 24, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1921, 312_1954, 312_1955)
  - Environmental Justice for All West Coast Tour -- Oakland, September 24, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1953)
  - Environmental Justice for All West Coast Tour -- San Francisco (Midway, Bayview), September 24, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1959)
  - Environmental Justice for All West Coast Tour -- Monterey College B-roll, September 25, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1965)
  - Environmental Justice for All West Coast Tour -- Sunnyvale, September 25, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1952)
  - Environmental Justice for All West Coast Tour -- Fort Ord, Fresno, Daly City, September 25-26, 2006 (Box 161, Minidv 312_1888, Box 162, Minidv 312_1950, 312_1957, 312_1964, 312_1966, 312_1969)
  - Environmental Justice for All West Coast Tour -- Delano, September 26-27, 2006 (Box 142, Minidv 312_1884, Box 162, Minidv 312_1938)
  - Environmental Justice for All West Coast Tour -- Temecula, Pala Tribe, Calixico, September 28-29, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1945, 312_1946, 312_1949, 312_1958, 312_1962)
  - Environmental Justice for All West Coast Tour -- Sunnyvale Interviews, September 29, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1963)
  - Environmental Justice for All West Coast Tour -- Pacoima, circa September-October, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1961)
  - Environmental Justice for All South Tour -- Anniston, circa September-October, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1931, 312_1932, 312_1934, 312_1941)
  - Environmental Justice for All South Tour -- Berea, Louisville, circa September-October, 2006 (Box 142, Minidv 312_1885, Box 161, Minidv 312_1892, 312_1905, Box 162, Minidv 312_1935, 312_1956)
  - Environmental Justice for All South Tour -- Biloxi, circa September-October, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1943)
  - Environmental Justice for All South Tour -- Charleston, Whitesville, circa September-October, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1922, 312_1930, 312_1933)
  - Environmental Justice for All South Tour -- Dixon, TN, circa September-October, 2006 (Box 161, Minidv 312_1890)
  - Environmental Justice for All South Tour -- Gulf Port, circa September-October, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1924)
  - Environmental Justice for All South Tour -- Knoxville, circa September-October, 2006 (Box 142, Minidv 312_1883)
  - Environmental Justice for All South Tour -- Moss Point, circa September-October, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1942)
  - Environmental Justice for All South Tour -- Port Arthur, Mossville, New Orleans, circa September-October, 2006 (Box 161, Minidv 312_1889, 312_1893, Box 162, Minidv 312_1916, 312_1923, 312_1940, 312_1944, 312_1960)
  - Environmental Justice for All South Tour -- San Pedro, circa September-October, 2006 (Box 162, Minidv 312_1951)
    9/30 - Dinner in San Pedro, 10/1 - Tours: Pacoima, Midland
  - Bush Crimes Teach-In, St. John the Divine, October 30, 2006 (Box 133, Dvcam 312_1017)
  - "Is It Worse Than You Think": WCW Teach-In, December 4, 2006 (Box 133, Dvcam 312_1016)
  - Code Pink Mothers Day Peace Vigil, 2006; cuid39628 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_394)
  - Deep Dish Awards, Featured Installations ad Screenings List, c. 2006 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - "Feminism and War" -- Conference, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Festival du Archéologique, Bordeaux, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - "Iraqi Women Speak Out" Tour, 2006; cuid39588 (Box 152, Minidv 312_1225, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_288)
  - Deep Dish 20th Anniversary Holiday Party, 2006; cuid39589 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_289)
  - Fajr International Film Festival, Tehran, 2006; cuid39590 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_290)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art -- Biennial Exhibition, 2006; cuid39582 (Box 53, Folder 3, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_291)
  - Impact 2012: A Festival of Political Art -- Panel Footage, 2006-2013; cuid39591 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_292)
    Presented by Culture Project; Includes footage of the following panels: "Blueprint for Accountability: Drone Warfare" with Medea Benjamin and Sara Knuckey, Moderated by Nermeen Shaikh; "A Conversation on Voter Suppression and Citizens United" with Isaiah Castilla, Diana Sen, and Mimi Marziani; "A Conversation on Economy" with Chris Hedges, Robert Johnson, Taylor Jo Isenberg, and Patrick Markee, Moderated by Sam Seder; Performances by the Civilians Investigative Theater Company; "Interactive Think Tank: Foreign Policy and the Media" with Nermeen Shaikh, Melik Kaylan, Jean Victor Nkolo, and Allan Buchman; "A Conversation on Immigration" with Jose Antonio Vargas, Cristina Jimenez, Karen Kaminsky, Rinku Sen, and Iyaba Ibo Mandingo
  - Impeachment Summit, February 17-19, 2007 (Box 147, Minidv 312_0907, 312_0908, 312_0909, 312_0910, 312_0911, 312_0912, 312_0914, Box 148, Minidv 312_0922, 312_0925, 312_0986)
  - The Archaeology Channel International Film and Video Festival, Eugene, Oregon, May 1-5, 2007; cuid39592 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_293)
  - The Committee for Open Discussion of Zionism Forum, "Transformation of Palestine/Israel into a Single, Secular, Democratic State..." -- Planning and Distribution, June 2008 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Rassegna Internazionale del Cinema Archeologico, Rovereto, October 1-6, 2007; cuid39593 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_294)
  - Cinema Vérité: Iran International DocumeCinema Vérité: Iran International Documentary Film Festival, Tehranntary Film Festival, Tehran, October 15-19, 2007; cuid39594 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_295)
  - INDIE SPACE Opening Film Festival, Seoul, South Korea, November 8-21, 2007 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Art Education Fundraising Event, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - David Barsamian Benefit Discussion, Brooklyn, New York, 2007; cuid39595 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_296)
  - Workshop on Archaeology and Computers -- Franz Schuller Interview Notes, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - "Access to Oxygen" Panel Discussion, 2008; cuid39596 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_298)
  - Committee for the Open Discussion of Zionism (CODZ) Conference Plans, 2008 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - "Expression = Life: ACT UP, Video and the AIDS Crisis" Panel Discussion, 2008; cuid39597 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_299)
  - NACLA 40th Celebration Video Interviews, 2008 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - "Signs of Change: Social Movement Cultures, 1960s to the Present" Exhibition, Exit Art, 2008; cuid39583 (Box 53, Folder 9, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_300)
  - "Shifting Focus" NYU Class, 2008-2010; cuid39598 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_301)
  - Peach Tree Screening, August 13, 2009 (Box 156, Minidv 312_1528)
  - "Behind the Bars" Screenings, 2009; cuid39599 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_302)
  - "Many Yesses One No" Panel Discussion, 2009; cuid39600 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_303)
  - "Resistencia y Solidaridad" Panel Discussion, NYU, 2009; cuid39601 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_304)
  - Edward Said Lecture at Columbia University, 2009; cuid39602 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_305)
  - International Longshoreman's Association Local 1588 Meeting, 2009; cuid39603 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_306)
  - Panel Discussion on Prison Industrial Complex, NYU, 2009; cuid39604 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_307)
  - DIY Media Screenings, NYU, 2009-2010; cuid39605 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_307)
  - "Gaza Reports Back from the Gaza Freedom March" Event Footage, Judson Memorial Church, 2009-2010; cuid39606 (Box 156, Minidv 312_1495, 312_1496, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_309)
  - MoMa Screener, February 12, 2010 (Box 156, Minidv 312_1516)
  - Arundhati Roy Live in San Francisco with David Barsamian and Alice Walker, March 27, 2010; cuid39629 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_395)
  - "Grassroots Media Network vs Immigrant Criminalization: Shifting the Debate" Forum, Detroit, Michigan, June 25, 2010; cuid39607 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_310)
  - "Acting Together on the World Stage: A Conference on Theatre and Peace Building in Conflict Zones", September 23-26, 2010; cuid39608 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_311)
  - Cultures of Resistance -- Lowkey, Shadia Mansour, and Norman Finkelstein Book Tour, 2010; cuid39611 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_315)
    Iraqi rapper Lowkey and Palestinian lyricist Shadia Mansour join Norman Finkelstein on his book tour
  - "Grassroots Networks and the Immigration Debate" Strategy Workshop, WSU, 2010; cuid39609 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_312)
  - "Hungry for Justice" Strike Photographs, 2010; cuid39610 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_313)
  - Miral Alwan Panel Footage, 2010; cuid39612 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_316)
  - "Re-Igniting the Network" Conference, 2010; cuid39584 (Box 53, Folder 10, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_314)
  - Liliana Yanez and Melisa, Dream Team at Lehman College, February 24, 2011 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1472)
  - Linda Green Keynote at Lehman College, February 24, 2011 (Box 156, Minidv 312_1485)
  - Alfonso Gonzalez, Alysha Galvez, and Liliana Yanez at Lehman College, February 24, 2011 (Box 156, Minidv 312_1486)
  - "Coming Out of the Shadows," Lehman College, March 16, 2011 (Box 156, Minidv 312_1473, 312_1474)
  - Left Forum -- "Neoliberalism in L.A.", March 19, 2011 (Box 156, Minidv 312_1478, 312_1479)
  - Left Forum -- Fez Panel, March 19, 2011 (Box 156, Minidv 312_1480, 312_1481)
  - Left Forum -- "Race and Racism: the Immigration Debate", March 19, 2011 (Box 156, Minidv 312_1487, 312_1488)
  - Left Forum -- "Farms and Agriculture" Interviews, March 19, 2011 (Box 156, Minidv 312_1489)
  - Left Forum -- Dream Act Panel, March 20, 2011 (Box 156, Minidv 312_1490, 312_1491)
  - Juliano Memorial, St Pauls, May 4, 2011 (Box 156, Minidv 312_1507, 312_1509, 312_1518)
  - Hiroshima Talk, December 7, 2011 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1471)
  - "Culture of Resistance" Lecture, NYU, 2011; cuid39613 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_317)
  - "Labor on the Edge" Panel Discussion, 2011; cuid39614 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_318)
  - Video Training Workshops, 2011; cuid39615 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_319)
  - Left Forum, 2012; cuid39616 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_320)
  - Maqam Arab Music Festival, 2012; cuid39617 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_321)
  - New School, February 10, 2012 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1468)
  - Boycott, Divestment, Sanctions (BDS) Panel Footage, October 23, 2013; cuid39619 (Box 148, Minidv 312_0945, 312_0947, 312_0948, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_323)
  - "The Gaza Monologues," New York City, 2013; cuid39618 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_322)
  - Left Forum, 2013; cuid39620 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_324)
  - Artist in Residency Program, 2014; cuid39621 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_325)
  - Images of the Other Conference, 2014 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1680, 312_1682, 312_1683, 312_1687)
  - Images of the Other Conference -- David Barsamian Interviews, circa 2014 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1669, 312_1670, 312_1671, 312_1672, 312_1673, 312_1674, 312_1675, 312_1676, 312_1678, 312_1690)
  - Images of the Other Conference -- "Eyewitness in Iraq" Keynote, Dahr Jamail, circa 2014 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1668)
    Produced by Pepperspray Productions
  - Immigration Dinners, 2014; cuid39622 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_326)
  - Left Forum -- "(En)gendering Hip Hop", 2014 (Box 147, Minidv 312_0920, Box 148, Minidv 312_0921)
  - Harriet's Apothecary Event Footage, 2015; cuid39623 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_327)
  - Jackson Rising New Economics Conference, 2015; cuid39624 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_328)
  - BAMcinématek Cinemaslam Event, Undated (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - "Being the Media," Panel, Undated (Box 157, Minidv 312_1533, 312_1534, 312_1536)
    Includes panel, presentation, interviews, and b-roll
  - Black Planet Productions' Not Channel Zero Series, Undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Blackside Inc., Malcolm X: Make It Plain -- Interview List, Undated (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Cuba TV Teach-In, Undated (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Cuban Film Program, Undated (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Curriculum Stills, Undated (Box 155, Minidv 312_1428)
  - "Divest" Lectures, Colorado University, November 13 (Box 157, Minidv 312_1580, 312_1581)
  - Heather Raffo Performance, Undated (Box 153, Minidv 312_1278)
    Shot by Persheng Vaziri; Content includes Artist plays different characters: artist who lived in Baghdad, bomb fell on house, famous for art and affairs; character who used to be a communist in Baghdad, lives in London
  - Hometown USA Video Festival -- Entry for Overall Excellence in Public Access Programming Videotape Log, Undated (Box 129, U-matic 312_0585)
  - "Hooking Up: Public Access Cable TV" -- Panel, Undated (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Larry Everest Talk at Rev Books, Undated; cuid39630 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_396)
  - The Lower East Side Festival of the Arts, Undated (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - National Alliance of Media Arts Centers Distribution Conference, Undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - National American Congress on Latin America -- Amerz, Undated (Box 154, Minidv 312_1341)
  - National American Congress on Latin America -- Camera A, Undated (Box 154, Minidv 312_1330, 312_1331, 312_1332, 312_1333, 312_1334, 312_1335, 312_1336, 312_1337, 312_1353, 312_1357)
  - National American Congress on Latin America -- Camera B, Undated (Box 154, Minidv 312_1342, 312_1343, 312_1344, 312_1345, 312_1346, 312_1347, 312_1348)
  - National American Congress on Latin America -- Dorfmann, Undated (Box 154, Minidv 312_1349)
  - National American Congress on Latin America -- Fred Goff, Undated (Box 154, Minidv 312_1340, 312_1352)
  - National American Congress on Latin America -- Gala, Undated (Box 154, Minidv 312_1355, 312_1358)
  - National American Congress on Latin America -- Hershberg, Undated (Box 154, Minidv 312_1338, 312_1354)
  - National American Congress on Latin America -- Rick Edwards, Undated (Box 154, Minidv 312_1351, 312_1356)
  - National American Congress on Latin America -- Volk, Undated (Box 154, Minidv 312_1339, 312_1350)
  - Posters for Film and Video Events, Undated (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - School of Hard Knocks Screening, Undated (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - "Television and You" Workshop, Center for Television Communications, Undated (Box 53, Folder 20)
- Series IV. Publicity, 1983-2017; 8.5 Linear Feet in 7 manuscript boxes and 5 flat boxes; 48 U-matic; 6 VHS; 6 Betacam_SP; 2 1_Inch_Video_Reel; 11 MiniDV; 1.96 Gigabytes in 1,324 files
  Series IV. Publicity (1983-2017) is arranged chronologically, with files grouped together by content type. Press releases and promotional materials are arranged together by Deep Dish series.
  Series IV. Publicity (1983-2017) includes materials related to Deep Dish TV's promotional and advertising activities. Paper and digital files include press releases, press clippings, Directories, mock-ups for logos and graphics, flyers and posters for Deep Dish programs, outreach to producers, programmers, and viewers, and files related to marketing and advertising. Analog and digital video recordings include demo reels, PSAs, promotions for programs and series.
  - Press Clippings, 1983-2006 (Box 53, Folder 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, Box 54, Folder 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, Box 55, Box 74, Folder 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, Box 75, Folder 1, 2, 3, Box 76, Folder 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, Box 77, Folder 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Press Clippings -- The Gulf Crisis TV Project, 1991-1992 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Press Clippings -- Democracy Now!, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Press Clippings -- Whitney Biennial, 2006; cuid39631 (Box 55, Folder 14, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_329)
  - Press Releases -- Paper Tiger TV, circa 1985 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases -- Deep Dish TV, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases -- "Labor Produces Access to Solidarity", 1986 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases -- The Opening Series, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases -- Directory, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases -- Hometown USA Award, July 24, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Press Releases -- Deep Dish Cooks Up Another Series, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Press Releases -- "Free Trade: A National Disaster", 1988 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Press Releases -- Green Screen: Grassroots Views of the Environmental Crisis, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Press Releases -- Public Access: Spigot for Bigots of Channels for Change?, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Press Releases -- ...Will Be Televised: Video Documents From Asia, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases -- The Gulf Crisis TV Project, 1990-1991 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases -- Fifth Anniversary Cablecast Event, June 17, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases -- "A Day Without Art" Live Performance, September 28, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases -- "No More War Toys", September 28, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases -- Roar! A Paper Tiger Mini TV Retrospective, September 28, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases -- Behind Censorship: The Assault on Civil Liberties, Spring 1992 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases -- Unheard Voices, March 1, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Press Releases -- Rock The Boat, August 1992 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases -- "In a Word, With Technology", October 27-November 17, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Press Releases -- L.A. Freewaves: Experimental Video from Southern California, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases -- "Not Channel Zero Hits the Road" Tour, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases -- Visions of Ourselves, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Press Releases -- Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired, May 6, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Press Releases -- "Netroots: Cultivating the Digital Park" Broadcast in Support of "Right of Way" Bill, July 21, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases -- Crime and Punishment: Youth Under Siege, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases -- Emergency Programming: Mumia Abu Jamal, August 3, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases -- Breaking Conventions, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases -- Bars and Stripes, May 30, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases -- Stolen Lives Project, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases -- Seattle Independent Media Center's Showdown in Seattle, November 30-December 4, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Press Releases -- Crashing the Party, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Press Releases -- Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation, 2004-2006; cuid39632 (Box 56, Folder 23, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_330)
  - Press Releases -- "Winter Soldier", 2008; cuid39641 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_331)
  - Press Releases -- Sick and Tired of Being Sick and Tired, 2009; cuid39642 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_332)
  - Press Releases -- We Interrupt This Program, 2018; cuid39643 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_333)
  - Press Conference at Boston Film / Video Foundation, April 16, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - CableVision Advertising Package, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Directory, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Flyer Design "Paste Ups", circa 1986 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - "Free Delivery" Newsletter Mock-ups, circa 1986 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - "Free Delivery" Newsletter, circa 1986 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - "Free Delivery" Newsletter, Spring 1987 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - "Free Delivery" Newsletter, Spring 1992 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - "Free Delivery" Newsletter, 2007-2008; cuid39644 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_334)
  - Publicity Feedback Forms, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - "Slice of the Pie" Flyer Mockup, circa 1986 (Box 75, Folder 4)